theworldsfinance.com 2015-05-03

# Privacy Policy | Finance

We respect the privacy of of all internet users.

Information collected

When you visit our website we collect some information from you. We collect no personally identifiable information such as your name, address, phone number, or e-mail address unless you willingly submit it to us via registration or contact. Some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use is collected upon your visit to our site in order to provide our advertisers with targeting information.

If yo were sent to our site from one of our partner sites and if you get sent to one of our partners from this site a non harmful cookie is added to your internet browser. These non-malicious cookies are set to delete themselves 1-24 hours after they have been created.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>
